(Raj:)Okay, in Avatar
when they have sex on Pandora...
(Raj:)...they hook up their ponytails.
(Raj:)So we know their ponytails
are like their junk.
(Howard:)Yeah. So?
(Raj:)When they ride horses
and fly on birds...
(Raj:)-...they also use their ponytails.
-Your point?
(Raj:)My point is if I were a horse or a bird I'd
be very nervous around James Cameron.
(Sheldon:)It amazes me how you constantly
obsess over fictional details...
...when there are important things
in the world to worry about.
(Sheldon:)For example, why wasn't William
Shatner in the new Star Trek movie?
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon,
I was up in the administration office...
(Leonard:)...and I happened to overhear
the name of the winner...
(Leonard:)...of the
Chancellor's Award for Science.
You wanna rub my nose in the fact my
contributions are being overlooked again?
(Sheldon:)I am the William Shatner
of theoretical physics.
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll play.
(Sheldon:)What self-important preening fraud
are they honoring this year?
(Leonard:)Oh, I'm so glad you asked it like that.
You.
(Sheldon:)-I won?
-You won.
(Sheldon:)I won.
(Sheldon:)This is astonishing.
(Sheldon:)Not that I won the award.
No one deserves it more.
(Sheldon:)Actually, I guess I misspoke.
It's not astonishing.
It's more like inevitable.
(Sheldon:)Not sure what to do.
Maybe call my mother.
Wait. I'm gonna conduct
an interview with myself...
(Sheldon:)...and post it online.
(Raj:)Well, good for him.
(Howard:)Yeah, the one thing
the William Shatner...
(Howard:)...of theoretical physics needed
was an ego boost.